motorcyclevalley.com 2018-06-10

# First and largest motorcycle website in Bangladesh. TVS Suzuki Pulsar Bajaj Yamaha Honda Hero. MotorcycleValley.com

**www.motorcyclevalley.com** is the best place where you can find all the important, essential and wishing information about motorcycles or bikes whenever you want wherever you want. So our user’s privacy is very important for us. We never use any kind of misuse with your any kind of information and of course not without your permission. We follow our strict privacy policy which is necessary to read every user before use our website (www.motorcyclevalley.com).  
The privacy policies are given below: 

**01\. Overview**  
The privacy practices are only available under the domain and sub domain of us (www.motorcyclevalley.com). By visiting in our site you must agree to our privacy policies and then you should access to our site (www.motorcyclevalley.com).If you do not agree to our privacy policies, it’s our heartiest recommendation that please do not use or access in to site (www.motorcyclevalley.com).This privacy policy contains the information use process or what happened to the information which we (www.motorcyclevalley.com) collect from users through our different services.

**02\. Cookies:**  
We (www.motorcyclevalley.com) collect cookies which are some pieces of data including in your hard drive containing your accessing information. We collect these cookies only to understand the time limit of our users and what their choices are actually reflected. Then we (www.motorcyclevalley.com) settle our plan including in mind the user choice and reflection. But when you don’t use it in mistreat. We only use in the way for the betterment of the users. 

**03\. One use of other user’s information:**  
In our site no one can use other user information. As www.motorcyclevalley.com is only a information provider website, so there is no chance to use any user’s information. Our registration based users can only use their perspective using information to access themselves. 

**04\. Use Email Tools:**  
You may not use the Email this Item to a friend or there are no email services. But it is sure that we (www.motorcyclevalley.com) do not use any kind permanent storing services to store your email address which you use to get any kind of information from us.

**05\. Password controlling:**  
You are the only one responsible person for your losing control over your password. We (www.motorcyclevalley.com) never disclose your any kind of user ID or password to any third party. The power of giving the user ID or Password is only depend on you. The way of sharing ID or Pass fall upon you to any third part is your personal decision. We (www.motorcyclevalley.com) are not responsible for any kind of this action. If you lose control over your id or pass for your any kind of your personal offense, you have to sure that we (www.motorcyclevalley.com) will never be responsible for your failure of accessing. 

**06\. Accessing or changing or removing personal information or account:**  
We give you the opportunity to change your personal information at any time you want. You do not need any kind of help from us to (www.motorcyclevalley.com) change your any information. Because it is almost very difficult to access manually into your account and makes any changes, besides it also goes against our (www.motorcyclevalley.com) terms of services. You have the full power to change the entire information what you give us (www.motorcyclevalley.com) to show publicly. You will able to change your user id name, your password, your other preferences, email address and setup section in (www.motorcyclevalley.com).Once you posted your changes you will not able to change them for certain times. After all of these if you need any kind of help, you can email your problem to (info@motorcyclevalley.com).We will take care of your problem and try to solve this.   
Besides above, if you want to delete or remove your any kind of your information you can do it very easily. Also you can delete or remove you full account and it is not difficult for you to do this. We (www.motorcyclevalley.com) can assure you that any kinds of delete information are never use in any action or any where or any third party.

**07\. Other sources information collection:**  
There is another thing that you have to know that in this document (privacy policy) we only disclosure of information that we collect from you and our policy not others third parties policies. To extend that you disclose your information to other or third parties or bidder or sellers or buyers, it will be followed by their privacy of policy not ours. We (www.motorcyclevalley.com) do not control other parties’ policies. So it is your decision to disclose your information to other parties. But our recommendation is that to ask question before you disclose your information to others.

**08\. No objection of spam; spyware; or spoofing**  
We (www.motorcyclevalley.com) or our honorable users do not tolerate any kind of spam. Make sure to set your Motorcyclevalle.com communication so that we can communicate to you as you prefer. You are authorizes to contact to other users without his/her permission. For reporting any kind of spam; spyware or spoofing you can contact us through our contact page.

**09\. Your rights**  
You have the right to inform us about our any kind of miss judgments. You can also report us to stop of any kind of information which you do not want to show in front of public or any wrong information that we publish not only yours but also in the entire website. It is our guarantee to establish your rights without any doubts.  
If you are concerned about your data you have the right to request access to the personal data which we may hold or process about you. You have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your data free of charge. At any stage you also have the right to ask us to stop using your personal data for direct marketing purposes. Carmudi.com.bd.   

**10\. Privacy review:**  
We want the better services for our users’ .so we made a privacy review to make understand what we actually trying to say in our whole privacy policy. So, we request our users to read our (www.motorcyclevalley.com) privacy policy review to make you better understand our way of speech.  
Notice  
We can amend this privacy policy at any time by positing these terms on the site. All these terms are effective automatically 30 days after they are initially posted on the site (www.motorcyclevalley.com)

  1. We never disclose your information without your permission.
  2. We only use cookies for understanding users’ choice for future update.
  3. Your personal information which is required for sign up is always protected from any kind of misuse.
  4. You can update your information at any time.
  5. You have to take all the responsibility to disclose your information to other third parties.
  6. You have always the superior right to remove your registered account from our site (motorcyclevalley.com)
  7. You cannot contact to our others users without his/her permission.
  8. You have the right to report us for any misconception in : info@motorcyclevalley.com
  9. No third parties can get your any kind of information like email; password; id; password from us (motorcyclevalley).

**11\. Notice:**  
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amend terms on the Site. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site.
